{"data":[{"question":"John came to see me ________ day. It was last Friday, I think.","a":"another","b":"other","c":"the next","d":"the odd","answer":"4","explain":"\n- The odd occasion\/day\/moment\/drink etc especially British English a few occasions, days etc that happen at various times but not often and not regularly.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"I met two strangers on the way to work. One of them greeted me and ________ didn't.","a":"others","b":"another","c":"others","d":"the other","answer":"4","explain":"\n- The other: used to refer to the second of two people or things, which is not the one you already have or the one you have already mentioned.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"He will ________ a special sale to get some new shirts.","a":"keep an eye on","b":"take track of","c":"take advantage of","d":"put an end to","answer":"3","explain":"\n-Take advantage of something (to do something): to use a particular situation to do or get what you want.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Some people like to have the windows open all the time; ________ don't.","a":"other","b":"another","c":"others","d":"the other","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Other: used to refer to all the people or things in a group apart from the one you have already mentioned or the one that is already known about.\u00a0\n- Don't- subject is plural.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"I can't see him today. I'll have to see him ________ day.","a":"another","b":"other","c":"the next","d":"the other","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Another: not the same thing, person etc, but a different one.\u00a0\n- Time (day) I will meet him has't been defined yet.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"We spent the night in a small village and continued our journey ________ day.","a":"another","b":"other","c":"the next","d":"the other","answer":"3","explain":"\n- The next day\/week etc (= on or during the following day, week etc).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Bill and ________ boys are playing in the yard. Jane and ________ girls are in the front room.","a":"others \/ another","b":"other \/ others","c":"the next \/ the next","d":"the other \/ the other","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Other: : used to refer to all the people or things in a group apart from the one you have already mentioned or the one that is already known about.\u00a0\n- The other + Noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"She ________ to the cinema last night.","a":"went over","b":"went on","c":"went out","d":"went off","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Go out: to leave your house, especially in order to enjoy yourself.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"I've been trying to ________ him all day.","a":"fall in love with","b":"take track of","c":"take advantage of","d":"get in touch with","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Get in touch with: talking or writing to someone.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"An ever-growing proportion of this ________ consists of unburned hydrocarbon gases from the exhausts of automobiles.","a":"pollute","b":"polluted","c":"pollution","d":"pollutant","answer":"3","explain":"\n- This + noun.\u00a0\n- Pollution: substances that make air, water, soil etc dangerously dirty.\u00a0\n- Pollutant: a substance that makes air, water, soil etc dangerously dirty, and is caused by cars, factories etc.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"}]}